は？
We are no different from the Ants.
これからは 「ネフェルピトー」って呼んでね。
No... We are far worse.
全師団長　兵隊長に告ぐ 全師団長　兵隊長に告ぐ
The poison, which spread
when the rose bloomed, was superior to similar toxins
これより軍団長ネフェルピトー殿 立ち会いの下 第一講堂において 授与式を執り行う
because it was immediately absorbed by
those in the area unfortunate enough to survive the explosion.
フフっ。 そこで諸君らは 多少の苦痛と引き換えに
Rapid destruction of their organs would begin, and their bodies themselves
莫大なパワーを得ることになる。 その力　遺憾なく 女王様のために発揮せよ！
would become poisons that continued to
emit new poison, until the victim died. The amount of poison for a lethal dose and
the amount of time until the subject died
奴らは真っすぐ進んでる。 この先にキメラアントの 巣があるとみて間違いない。 すげぇな。 あれから一瞬も外さずに ずっと捉え続けてる。
In other words, it was a demonic weapon
more inhumane than any other.
そして　ゲームをクリアした後 カイトに会わせたのも…。 ジン！
The Word x Is x That Someone
ジンがカイトと俺達を 会わせた後のことを
Th-This is...
どれだけ予測していたかは 分からない。
What is happening to my body?
きっと　ゴンも気に入るってことは 確信してたはずだ。
Pouf.
そして　絶対　カイトに ついて行くだろうってことも。 「カイトと一緒に旅をして もっと強くなれ」ってことだね。
Is something the matter, Meruem-sama?
修行の場にしちゃ かなりシビアだけどな。 だからこそ　俺は　お前達に
Have you changed your mind?
何度も覚悟を問うて来た。 あっ。 あっ。
In that case, we must evacuate you at once.
前に　お前達が言った通り ジンさんは　俺に何かを期待して お前達を 託したのかもしれない。
Your Majesty? Even when I can see right through him, he still refuses to divulge his secret.
だが俺は　お前達をこの旅で 鍛え上げようなんて思ってない。 そんな余裕もない。
Very well. I only have to capture the remaining intruders.
俺は　お前達が使えると 思ったから連れて来ただけだ。
I am very curious about your secret now.
あとは　お前達自身の覚悟の問題。
You do not intend to change your
mind about telling me, do you?
覚悟があれば　「念」も上達するし 戦いにも強くなるだろう。 逆に　そうならねば アリに食われて死ぬだけだ。
I will keep my word, even if it costs me my life.
だが　死ぬわけにはいかない。
Good.
それは　「ハンター十ヶ条」の 其乃一にも 厳然と定められている。
He's already using his final
permissible En search!
狩りとは 狙った者と狙われた者
I can see
互いの覚悟のぶつかり合いだ。
everything. I see what has changed since
the first time I used En.
互いに覚悟を持って　ぶつけ合い 勝敗を決するのが狩りだ。
The footprints that were not there before.
負ければ 相手のおきてやルールに従い 多くの場合　命を奪われる。
An abandoned vehicle.
ルール…。
Youpi's corpse.
それが嫌なら勝つしかない。
A door that has been opened.
「念」の上達は　もちろん 敵を知り　己を知ることこそ
And someone responding to my
En who did not previously.
だから　だから　あの時カイトは 俺を殴ってくれたんだね。
Huh?!
ヘビブナの群生地に 入る奴があるか！))
Was it you who killed Youpi?
((見ろ　子連れのキツネグマが残す 縄張のシグナルだ))
A-Absolutely not! I am a mere Squadron Leader!
((これを見たら どんな　のんきな動物も 隣山まで逃げるほど ヤバいもんだ！))
I would never have any reason to kill Youpi-dono! Youpi-dono
あれも森のおきて ルールだもんね。
was talking to me when he
suddenly coughed up blood, became overcome with pain, and died.
ジンに代わって ルールを教えてくれた。
I swear that I'm not lying! I'm not lying...
あぁ…。 ん？ ん？ そうだ　思い出した。
But before he could answer my question...
ハンターライセンス？ これは？
He died.
ジンさんのだ。 えっ　ジンの？
I believe that he must have been hit
俺の最終試験の課題 覚えているか？
by some sort of attack before encountering me.
うん　ジンを捜し当てること。
That's why I came here to
investigate if any intruders
その試験が始まる前に ジンさんに渡されたんだ。
are hidden in the crowd.
「こいつを使って 俺を捜してみろ」ってな。
The Royal Guard Pouf...
ジンさんを捜し当てた時 返そうと思ったんだが…。 え？　受け取らなかったの？
He's going to be trouble. I'm pretty sure he has the
ability to read my mind.
いや　今の今まで忘れてた。
Welfin is a serious threat.
えっ…。 んが…。
I have no idea what he might tell the King...
ゴン　お前　ジンさんは 自分で捜すって言ってたよな。
Simply telling him to keep quiet
would be too lenient. I should eliminate him immediately!
えっ…　うん。 ならば　必ず捜し出せ。
I should accuse him of being a traitor,
and execute him on the spot.
そして　お前から そいつを返しておいてくれないか。
In any case, I must get him away from the King.
うん　まずは　カイトと一緒に この仕事をやり遂げて
Meruem-sama, he is—
もっともっと強くなってから…。
I know what you want to say.
そしたら必ず　ジンを見つけて これを返すよ。
I can now sense the emotions of
any that my En has touched.
約束する。 頼んだぞ。
I could feel his unbridled hostility toward me.
さぁ　先を急ぐぞ。
In... Incredible...
奴らを見失う。
Once someone has been exposed to my En, I can see into their mind by simply looking.
おら！ 次！
So it wasn't just Youpi's wings and attacks.
凡夫って大変だな
The King also inherited my Spiritual Message...
こんな面倒なことしなきゃ 能力を引き出せないなんて
And he's made it infinitely more powerful.
ウフフ…
Your Majesty!
ペギー　あとを頼むね。
The King is invincible...
どちらへ？
The King is unrivaled!
確かめて来る 僕が　どれだけ強いか。
And yet... Why?!
化け物だ。
Why is my heart
何てことだ　信じられん。
filled with
どうしたの？　カイト。 ゴン　キルア　すぐ逃げろ。
such unease?
え？ え？ 早く行け　ここから離れろ！
Now there is some fear mixed in, but there is no concealing
your desire to kill me.
見っけた。
what drives your hatred of me.
俺から離れろ！
Speak.
あ！ あ！
This is no time to let emotion
get the better of me!
う…。 う…。
You must follow the proper order.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。 うぁ!!
He has deep ties to my secret.
バッ…！
However, he does not realize this.
いい判断だ　キルア。
If you continue questioning him, it is very likely that he will reveal
アッハッハッハ…。
I believe that you would not want your reward before winning the contest.
絶体絶命のピンチだな。 いい目が出ろよ！
I will keep my secret hidden using only truth!
ドゥルルル…　３。 へぇ　そんなこともできるの。
If you wish to continue our contest, I believe you should wait to question him.
俺達は　うぬぼれていた
I should have run away right off the bat. Temptation got the better of me!
２人合わせて 片腕を失ったカイト以下
When I saw the giant Youpi
shrunken down like some bug, and then he dropped dead, I actually had the delusion that I could be King... So I stayed...
奴は　そう判断した
I was drunk on my delusion!
それが現実
I felt almighty, like some sheltered little kid.
恐らく　カイト１人なら こんなことにはならなかった くっ…。
I felt alive. Yeah, I'm an idiot! I was drunk!
俺達は　大バカだ
Too many things happened simultaneously,
and then I remembered Gyro.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
What tools do I have left?
ハァ　ハァ…。
The message? Pouf's secret?
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。 [TEL]
Will it be enough to save me? What do I say? The first...
ハァ　ハァ…。 [TEL]
The first word I say is key.
えっ　カイトを 置いて来た!?　一体どうして！ 一体どういうこと？ 何でか　ちゃんと説明して！
Just one word will decide
whether I live or die. If I choose the wrong one, it's all over!
うん　分かった とにかく　そこで待ってて。
This overwhelming pressure. This abnormal tension.
僕達も　ちょうど そっちに向かってるんだ。
Pouf, does that secret
あっ…。
without waiting for Pouf to speak.
ネテロ会長
Despite the understanding that he
had Pouf's unwavering loyalty, the murderous aura visibly
emanating from the King
何だ　ガキじゃねえか。
indicated that Pouf would have no choice
物見遊山で首突っ込むから やけどするんだよ。 さっさと　お家に帰んな。
but to atone with his death if that answer
was not what the King wanted.
かわいそうでしょう。
were equally meaningless before the King.
相手は　ただの子供なんだから。
No one could stop him.
ホッホッホ…！ 随分と　ヘコんでおるのぉ。
Even then, I was already
そんなに敵は　手ごわかったか？ くっ…！
prepared to die.
「念」を使える奴がいた。
to my own loyalty.
今まで会った誰よりも 薄気味悪いオーラだった。
There is nothing that I can say.
兄貴より。
Though the contest has yet to conclude.
自分で「念」を覚えてみて よく分かる。
That is all there is to it...
あんた達も　すごく強い。 それでも　あいつに 勝てる気がしない。
His incredible resolve and madness
フッ。
stopped the King.
君は今　一種のパニック状態に 陥っている。
I am hungry.
あとは私達に任せて ゆっくりベッドで休むことですよ。
However...
ハッハッハ…！ 言ってることは 俺と一緒じゃねえかよ　ノヴ。
Welfin immediately understood...
フッ。
I am...
坊ず　念使い同士の戦いに
I am going to be eaten!
お前は　ずれてるんだよ。 相手の能力が　どんなものか 分からないのが普通。
One second later...
ほんの一瞬の緩み　怯みが
I'm dead!
一発逆転の致命傷になる。 一見したオーラの総量が 多い少ないなんて
Upon learning his fate, Welfin instantly appeared
to age one hundred years.
気休めにもならねえ。
I want to live.
勝敗なんて たゆたってて当たり前。 それが「念」での戦闘。 だが　それでも
That was when his past rapidly
flashed through his mind
１００％勝つ気でやる。
and then scattered, the fragments
mingling with his present.
それが念使いの気概ってもんさ。
One word...
相手のオーラに気おされ 逃げた時点で　お前は失格。
My first and last!
敗者以下だ。 モラウ　もういい。
Caught between the desire to live
and unavoidable death...
ゴンは　寝とるのか？
One word...
敵を攻撃しようとしたから 腕ずくで止めた。
The message for the King! One word!
手加減する余裕なかったから いつ目が覚めるか…。
What Pouf discussed with Pitou! One word!
ハッハッハ　そっちの坊ずは まだ見込みがあるな。
Pouf's secret! One word!
モラウ。
I...
巨大キメラアントが 人を食うという信じ難い話。
One word! ...won't die until I'm dead!
事実である以上 全力で被害拡大を防がねばならぬ。 中途半端な戦力は 敵に吸収される恐れがある。
As his brain cells began working
harder than ever before, he made a choice that he never would
have in normal circumstances.
ああ。
Komugi?
((相手のオーラに気おされ 逃げた時点で　お前は失格))
He values her more than I feared. Punish me for my actions.
俺は…　失格
No words are needed.
キルア。 あっ。
We are one now. There will be no punishment.
ありがとう。
I never had a chance...
何だよ　「ありがとう」って。
Continue searching for Pitou. The two captured intruders
may have information.
俺を止めてくれたの キルアだろ？
Once you are done, release them. I have nothing else to ask them.
あのまま俺が暴走してたら カイトの邪魔してた。
All I can do is nod.
そうすれば　３人とも危なかった。
Yes. The opened door...
でも　俺はカイトを見殺しにした。
And footprints leading inside.
カイトは生きてる！
The resolve of the two that I sensed with my En.
あんな奴には　絶対
All signs lead to one conclusion.
絶対に負けない。
Welfin...
でも　あれだけのケガ 奴を倒しても　すぐには動けず
Y-Yes! Komugi is in the underground warehouse
with the woman and the octopus.
どこかに身を潜めて待ってる。
Your job was to deliver that information
to me or the Royal Guard.
俺達が戻って来るのを。
H-How did you know that?
だから　早く戻ろう　強くなって。
I believe the octopus was the
reason you accepted this job. There was a different reason
why you did not complete it.
カイトを助けに！
Is that reason the cause of your hatred for me?
ゴン…
So it is. Do not worry.
お前は光だ
Once you answer my question,
you are free to go wherever you wish.
時々　まぶし過ぎて 真っすぐ見られないけど
They said that they're waiting in Bizeff's
private courtyard, in Area D.
行こう！
Gyro is the only man I'll ever call King! You... All of you...
強くなって。
Are enemies! Our enemies!
城に冷凍庫を用意せよ
And if possible, I hope you can live as a human.
うん。 僕　ちょっと強いかも。
Netero once believed that the King was wavering
between human and Ant. But now...